Oregon Department of Transportation City Maps
Geography & Map Division Library of Congress
Town Plan Maps of Oregon 1986-
Oregon. Dept. of Transportation
maps: col.; 64 x 44 cm. or smaller, on sheets 70 x 49 cm. or smaller. Scales differ.
Geography & Map Division Library of Congress Washington, DC
City maps issued by the Oregon Department of Transportation showing highways, streets, parks, railroads, schools, public buildings, section corners, water features, land features, and various boundaries.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically therein.
Organizations
Oregon. Department of Transportation.
Subjects
Cities and towns--Oregon--Maps.; Roads--Oregon--Maps.
Administrative Information
Source
Deposited in the Library of Congress, Geography & Map Division by the Oregon Department of Transportation, 1990-
Accrual Frequency
Maps are received on an irregular and ongoing basis.
Electronic
Some items are available on the Internet from Oregon Dept. of Transportation at http://www.oregon.gov/ODOT/TD/TDATA/gis/CityMaps.shtml.
Scope and Content Note
This finding aid lists maps of incorporated towns issued by the Oregon Department of Transporation and held in the Geography & Map Division. The dates within the list represent the holdings of the Division. These city maps show highways, streets, parks, railroads, schools, public buildings, section corners, water features, land features, and various boundaries. The list is arranged alphabetically by city name.
http://lccn.loc.gov/96682185
Inventory
- Adair Vilage (Benton County) 6/1991 2002
- Adams (Umatilla County) 10/1990 6/1999 2002
- Adrian (Malheur County) 12/1990 10/1999 2002
- Albany (Linn and Benton Counties) 5/2000
- Amity (Yamhill County) 10/1992 2002
- Antelope (Wasco County) 1/1991 11/1994 3/2002
- Arlington (Gilliam County) 2/1992 12/1993 2002
- Ashland (Jackson County) 7/1999
- Astoria (Clatsop County) 11/1998 7/2000
- Athena (Umatilla County) 10/1990 2/2000
- Aumsville (Marion County) 12/1997 9/2000
- Aurora (Marion County) 2/1991 8/1995 2002
- Baker City (Baker County) 12/1997 2002
- Bandon (Coos County) 10/1999 2002
- Banks (Washington County) 11/1999 2002
- Barlow (Clackamas County) 3/1991 5/1994 2002
- Bay City (Tillamook County) 8/1999
- Beavorton (Washington County) 11/1999 2002
- Bend (Deschutes County) 1/1993 2002
- Boardman (Morrow County) 1/1991 11/1999
- Bonanza (Klamath County) 2/2000 1/2002
- Brookings (Curry County) 12/1990 3/2000 2002
- Brownsville (Linn County) 9/1999 8/2000
- Burns (Harney County) 8/1990 12/1990 12/1994 2002, See also Hines
- Butte Falls (Jackson County) 12/1997 7/2000
- Canby (Clackamas County) 2/1986 2002 1/2002
- Canyon City (Grant County) 4/1991 2002
- Cannon (Clatsop County) 8/1990 8/1998
- Canyonville (Douglas County) 3/2000 2002
- Carlton (Yamhill County) 10/1992 2002
- Cascade Locks (Hood River) 3/2000 2002
- Cave Junction (Josephine County) 9/1990 12/1997 2002 12/2001
- Central Point (Jackson County) 5/2000 8/2000
- Chiloquin (Klamath County) 11/1999
- Clatskaine (Columbia County) 7/1998 2002
- Coburg (Lane County) 12/1997 2002
- Columbia City (Columbia County) 8/1999 9/2000 2002
- Condon (Gilliam County) 4/1986 9/2000 2002
- Coos Bay (Coos County) 3/2000 8/2000 2002
- Coquille (Coos County) 3/2000 2002
- Cornelius (Washington County) 11/1999 2002
- Corvallis (Benton County) 3/1986 8/2000 4/2002
- Cottage Grove (Lane County) 5/2000 2002
- Cove (Union County) 5/1991 4/2000
- Creswell (Lane County) 1/1991
- Culver (Jefferson County) 12/1999 6/2000
- Dallas (Polk County) 7/1997
- Damascus (Portland and Vicinity) 12/1999
- Dayton (Yamhill County) 10/1992
- Dayville (Grant County) 3/2000 2002
- Depoe Bay (Lincoln County) 12/1997
- Detroit (Marion County) 9/1990 12/1997 8/2000
- Dixie Mountain (Portland and Vicinity) 8/1999
- Donald (Marion County) 8/1999
- Drain (Douglas County) 10/1990 5/1999 2002
- Dufur (Wasco County) 12/1990 9/1999
- Dundee (Yamhill County) 10/1992 2002
- Dunes City (Lane County) 2/2000
- Durham (Washington County) 11/1999 2002
- Eagle Point (Jackson County) 11/1990 5/2000
- Echo (Umatilla County) 10/1990 8/1999 5/2002
- Elgin (Union County) 5/1991 3/2000
- Elkton (Douglas County) 11/1990 8/1999 2002
- Enterprise (Wallowa County) 11/1999
- Estacada (Clackamas County) 12/1997 2002
- Eugene East Quad (Lane County) 4/1991
- Eugenr West Quad (Lane County) 4/1991
- Fairview (Multnomah County) 11/1990 2002
- Falls City (Polk County) 5/2000
- Florence (Lane County) 10/1992
- Forest Grove (Washington County) 11/1999 2002
- Fossil (Wheeler County) 11/1999 3/2002
- Garibaldi (Tillamook County) 12/1997
- Gaston (Washington County) 11/1999
- (Linn County) 3/2000
- Gearhart (Clatsop County) 7/1999 2002
- Geravis (Marion County) 12/1990 12/1995
- Gladstone (Clackamas County) 12/1999 2002
- Glendale (Douglas County) 3/2000 2002
- Gold Beach (Curry County) 12/1990 8/2000 2002
- Gold Hill (Jackson County) 12/1997
- Granite (Grant County) 9/1999 2002
- Grants Pass (Josephine County) 12/1997
- Grass Valley (Sherman County) 11/1988
- Greenhorn (Baker County) 2/1992 2002
- Gresham (Multnomah County) 8/1988
- Haines (Baker County) 12/1997 2002
- Halfway (Baker County) 11/1999 2002
- Halsey (Linn County) 7/1999
- Happy Valley (Clackamas County) 12/1999 2002 12/2001
- Hardman (Morrow County) 1/1991
- Harrisburg (Linn County) 3/2000 3/2002
- Helix (Umatilla County) 10/1990 7/1998
- Heppner (Morrow County) 1/1991 3/2000
- Hermiston (Umatilla County) 5/1990 10/1990
- Hillsboro (Washington County) 11/1999 2002
- Hines (Harney County) 12/1990 4/2000 2002, See also Burns
- Hood River (Hood River) 9/1990 8/1998 2002
- Hubbard (Marion County) 3/2000 2002
- Huntington (Baker County) 9/1990 12/1997 2002
- Idanha (Marion County) 8/1999
- Imbler (Union County) 5/1991 12/1995
- Independence (Polk County) 8/1999
- Ione (Morrow County) 1/1991 1/994 3/2002
- Irrigon (Morrow County) 1/1991 5/2000 3/2002
- Island City (Union County) 10/1995
- Jacksonville (Jackson County) 12/1997
- Jefferson (Marion County) 2/1991
- John Day (Grant County) 12/1993 2002
- Johnson City (Clackamas County) 12/1999 2002
- Jordan Valley (Malheur County) 10/1999
- Joseph (Wallowa County) 10/1999
- Junction City (Lane County) 1/1991 10/2000 2002
- Keizer (Marion County) 3/1992
- King City (Washington County) 11/1999 2002 1/2002
- Klamath Falls (Klamath County) 2/1992 2002
- La Grande (Union County) 5/1991 3/2000
- Lafayette (Yamhill County) 10/1992 2002
- Lake Oswego (Clackamas County) 12/1999
- Lakeside (Coos County) 12/1992 2002
- Lakeview (Lake County) 3/2000 2002
- Lebanon (Linn County) 8/1999 6/2000
- Lexington (Morrow County) 1/1991
- Lincoln City (Lincoln County) 4/2000
- Lonerock (Gilliam County) 2/2000 2002
- Long Creek (Grant County) 8/1990 12/1997 2002
- Lostine (Wallowa County) 9/1990 12/1997
- Lowell (Lane County) 5/1999 2002
- Lyons (Linn County) 7/1999
- Madras (Jefferson County) 5/2000
- Malin (Klamath County) 12/1997
- Manzanita (Tillamook County) 12/1998
- Maupin (Wasco County) 3/2000
- Maywood Park (Multnomah County) 3/2000
- McMinville (Yamhill County) 10/1992 2002
- Meachman/Umapine (Umatilla County) 10/1990
- Medford (Jackson County) 12/1994 7/2002
- Merrill (Klamath County) 12/1997
- Metolius (Jefferson County) 12/1997
- Mill City (Linn and Marion Counties) 8/1999 8/2000 2002
- Millersburg (Linn County) 12/1997
- Milton-Freewater (Umatilla County) 10/1990 8/1999
- Milwaukee (Clackamas County) 11/1987 2002 2/2002
- Mitchell (Wheeler County) 6/2000
- Molalla (Clackamas County) 7/1999 6/2000 2002
- Monmouth (Polk County) 9/1989 3/2002
- Monroe (Benton County) 7/1999 2002
- Monument (Grant County) 3/2000 2002
- Moro (Sherman County) 12/1997
- Mosier (Wasco County) 12/1997
- Mt. Angel (Marion County) 2/1991 2002
- Mt. Vernon (Grant County) 2/2000 2002
- Myrtle Creek (Douglas County) 7/1991 2002
- Myrtle Point (Coos County) 9/1990 2/2000 2001 2002
- Nehalem (Tillamook County) 7/1991 2001
- Newburg (Yamhill County) 5/1999 2001 2002
- Newport (Lincoln County) 8/1999 9/2000
- North Bend (Coos County) 3/2000 2002
- North Plains (Washington County) 11/1999 2002
- North Powder (Union County) 5/1991 3/1995 2001
- Nyssa (Malheur County) 8/1990 8/1999 5/2000
- Oakland (Douglas County) 11/1990 12/1990 2002
- Oakridge (Lane County) 9/1990 12/1997 2001
- Ontario (Malheur County) 12/1999 printed 8/2000 printed 3/2002
- Oregon City (Clackamas County) 11/1999 2002
- Paisley (Lake County) 3/2000 2002
- Pendleton (Umatilla County) 10/1990 3/1995 5/2001, varient edition also dated 10/1990
- Philomath (Benton County) 9/1990 12/1997 2001 2002
- Phoenix (Jackson County) 12/1997 6/2000
- Pilot Rock (Umatilla County) 10/1990 3/2000 2001
- Port Orford (Curry County) 11/1990 9/1999 2002
- Portland (Portland and Vicinity) 1/2000
- Powers (Coos County) 3/2000 2002
- Prairie City (Grant County) 3/2000 2001 2002
- Prescott (Columbia County) 3/1992 1/2002 00/2002
- Prineville (Crook County) 10/1990 2/2000 2001 2002
- Rainer (Columbia County) 4/1992 2/2000 2002
- Redmond (Deschutes County) 8/1999 7/2000 2001 2002
- Reedsport (Douglas County) 9/1990 5/1999 6/2000 2002
- Richland (Baker County) 7/1998 1/2002 00/2002
- Riddle (Douglas county) 9/1990 10/1999 1/2002 00/2002
- Rivergrove (Clackamas and Washington Counties) 9/1987
- Rockaway Beach (Tillamook County) 8/1999 2001
- Rogue River (Jackson County) 12/1997 2002
- Roseburg (Douglas County) 5/1990 2002
- Rufus (Sherman County) 12/1997
- St. Helens (Columbia County) 7/1993 2002
- St. Paul (Marion County) 12/1997 1/2002
- Salem East (Salem and Vicinity) 3/1992
- Salem West (Salem and Vicinity) 3/1992
- Sandy (Clackamas County) 12/1991 2002
- Sauvie Island 7/1999
- Scappoose (Columbia County) 12/1997 6/2000 2001 2002
- Scio (Linn County) 12/1990 10/1999 2002
- Scotts Mills (Marion County) 12/1997 2002
- Seaside (Clatsop County) 11/1990 2/1995 2002 4/2002
- Seneca (Grant County) 1/1991 6/2002
- Shady Cove (Jackson County) 10/1998 2002
- Shaniko (Wasco County) 12/1997 1/2002
- Sheridan (Yamhill County) 2/1995 2002
- Sherwood (Washington County) 5/1999 8/2000
- Siletz (Lincoln County) 12/1997
- Silverton (Marion County) 2/2000 2002 12/2001
- Sisters (Deschutes County) 3/2000 2002 12/2001
- Sodaville (Linn County) 10/1990 12/1997
- Spray (Wheeler County) 9/1990 10/1998 1/2002
- Springfield (Lane County) 4/1991
- Stanfield (Umatilla County) 10/1990 5/1995 4/2002
- Stayton (Marion County) 2/1995 6/2002
- Sublimity (Marion County) 7/1992 2002 4/2002
- Summerville (Union County) 5/1991 12/1993 2002
- Sumpter (Baker County) 12/1997 2002
- Sutherlin (Douglas County) 8/1990 7/1995 2002 4/2002
- Sweet Home (Linn County) 8/1998 6/2000 2002 1/2002
- Talent (Jackson County) 12/1997 4/2002
- Tangent (Linn County) 5/1991 4/2002
- The Dallas (Wasco County) 12/1997 4/2002
- Tigard (Washington County) 11/1999 4/2002
- Tillamook (Tillamook County) 11/1990 7/1993 12/2001
- Toledo (Lincoln County) 10/1990 9/1999
- Troutdale (Multnomah County) 1/2000 1/2002
- Tualatin (Clackamas and Washington Counties) 7/1988 2002 4/2002
- Turner (Marion County) 3/1992 2002
- Ukiah (Umatilla County) 10/1990 8/1998 1/2002
- Umatilla (Umatilla County) 10/1990 4/1995 4/2002
- Union (Union County) 5/1991 5/1991 3/2002, Variant second ed.
- Unity (Baker County) 3/2000 2002
- Vale (Malheur County) 12/1997 8/2000
- Veneta (Lane County) 5/1990 1/1993 2002 4/2002
- Vernonia (Columbia County) 2/2000 2002
- Waldport (Lincoln County) 11/1990 7/1998 2002
- Wallowa (Wallowa County) 12/1997
- Warrenton (Clatsop County) 8/1999 2002
- Wasco (Sherman County) 12/1997
- Waterloo (Linn County) 6/1990 12/1997 4/2002
- West Linn (Clackamas County) 2/1989 2002 3/2002
- Westfir (Lane County) 10/1990 6/1999
- Weston (Umatilla County) 10/1990 8/1998
- Wheeler (Tillamook County) 8/1999
- Willamina (Yamhill County) 10/1992 2002
- Wilsonville (Washington County) 6/1990 2002
- Winston (Douglas County) 7/1994 2002 5/2002
- Wood Village (Multnomah County) 3/2000 2002
- Woodburn (Marion County) 1/1991 8/1993 2002
- Yachats (Lincoln County) 3/1991
- Yamhill (Yamhill County) 10/1992
- Yoncalla (Douglas County) 7/1999 2002 5/2002